twitchfilm.net 2012-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Twitch

Revised: August 1, 2009 

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that Twitchfilm, LLC ("Twitch," "Service Provider," "we" or "our") treats the information You provide, either directly or indirectly, while accessing any website owned or controlled by Twitch ("Website" or "Websites"). Please read this statement carefully before using or accessing our Websites, since your use of and/or registration on any aspect of our Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Website. Also, please be aware that our Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation sites linked to from our Website, cookies placed on you computer by third party advertisers on our site, or third parties providing services to our Website. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Twitch only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers 

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well. 

I. TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION 

1\. Personally Identifying Information  
Our Websites generally collect personally identifying information you directly submit to us with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you register for any portion of our services or send us an email for one of our contests, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age, location, or gender may also be requested. 

We use personally identifying information you directly supply through the Website to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you create an account on our Website, we may use your e-mail address to send you notifications that relate to your account. Likewise, if you enter an online sweepstakes, we will use your supplied personally identifying information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use personally identifying information you supply to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. 

Additionally, we may use personally identifying information you supply in cookies we place on your computer. For example, if you login to our Website and you request to be remembered, your login and encrypted password will be stored in that cookie. Please be cognizant that that the presence of our cookie could be tracked or accessed by third-parties or affiliates. 

Unless otherwise specified on the Website or stated in relation to a specific promotion, we will not sell, share, trade, or otherwise provide any personally identifying information you have given us to any third-party or affiliate. We do reserve the right to allow access to our database by contracted third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance and hosted software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. 

If you do not wish to receive future communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail; or if you've registered on any part of the Website and you received communications pursuant to your account, please use the mechanism on the Website that allows you to change or update your email preferences and contact information or remove your account. 

There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the site that may be managed or participated in by third parties, such as e-commerce. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies. 

We may also provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process. 

2\. Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
Our servers, like most web servers, create log files, which contain information about your computer and your Internet connection that is transmitted when you visit and use our Website. This information includes, but is not limited to the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, your screen resolution, the website that referred you, the page you left the site on, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is usually associated with the location from which you access the Internet, like your local Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may also be tracking the links you click and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user's movement. 

We generally analyze this type of information in the aggregate to gather broad demographic information and look overall usage patterns in order to improve our Website. 

We also employ third parties to track and capture this same Non-Personally Identifiable Information in order to validate our own internal measurements, allow us access to deeper analysis tools then we have available on our server, and to allow independent verification of usage to our advertisers. Please be aware that our Privacy Policy does not cover information collected by these third parties. 

We reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, in concert information which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website. 

While your personally identifying information is protected as outlined above, we do reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

3\. Business Transition Notice  
As our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by Twitch, its parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website and the Website users may be among the transferred assets. 

II. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING & COOKIES 

The ads appearing on our Website are delivered to you by a number of affiliates and Third-Parites, including, but not limited to: Indieclick/3Jane, Google/Doubleclick, Tribal Fusion, and Tailsweep. These and other companies set cookies on your computer to gather information about your visit to our site and other sites. These cookies contain among other data the number of times you have viewed an ad, but do not contain your username, date of birth, or any other personal information. 

These cookies and the information they contain are used to serve contextually relevant advertising to you. We have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for our ad reps to set cookies for advertising. 

If you do not want the benefits of these advertising cookies or receiving focused advertising, you may be able to opt-out by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp 

If you don't want any cookies, your Web browser likely has an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of our Website may not function properly. 

III. INFORMATION SECURITY AND NOTIFICATION 

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, we can not guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases. By using our Website, you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use our Website. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you by e-mail, provided we have your e-mail address, or by public disclosure on this page and elsewhere on our Website, or both. 

IV. ACCESS BY CHILDREN 

This Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 18, and especially those under age 13. No one under age 18 is allowed to provide any personal information, register for accounts, or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Parents, if your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website or create accounts to message other members, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so. If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below: 

Twitchfilm, LLC  
ATTN: Privacy Policy Coordinator  
4223 Glencoe Ave.  
Suite B119  
Marina Del Rey, CA 90292  
Fax: (310) 827-7690  
E-mail: privacy (hat or at) twitchfilm {dot} net  

If you don't agree to the terms contained in this Privacy Policy, please exit the Website by closing this window or clicking the Back button on your browser until you return to a page not under the control of the Service Provider.
